RESUME

VIJAY SINGH

MOB: +917007621412

+919839096049

EMAIL: vijsin10@gmail.com

.....

OBJECTIVE

To secure an appropriate position this will provide growth opportunities with effective utilization of my skills and experiences also the opportunity to learn more in professional atmosphere.

SUMMARY

7 years experience in sales & marketing of mortgage and building materials.

An effective communicator possessing excellent presentation & soft skills with honed marketing management logical and problem solving abilities. Recognized for successfully meet targets, proficiently formulating and implementing budgets, building high performing teams and nurturing fruitful relationship with customers.

EMPLOYMENT DETAILS

1. UPAL SUPERCENTER, MOHANLALGANJ, LKO.

Store Incharge - Cera, Johnson & Johnson Marbonite, Kajaria Eternity Feb2021 Aug 2021 (7 Months).

Showroom Sales, Team Handling, Devlopment and Training of Team Members, Store And Their Products Management, Tiles And Sanitary Ware.

2. A.J. ENTERPRISES. LUCKNOW

Sales Officer - Tiles Sales(Kajaria Eternity)

Aug2018 - March 2020 (1 Years 7Months)

Tiles Sales, Team Handling, Project Sales, Institutional Sales, Pay Collection, Proper Execution of Order And Dispatch It On Time. Followup For Payment. Develop New Sample For Client. Maintain Good Relation With Client.

3.AXIS SECURITIES LTD. GURGAON

Relationship Officer (E2) - Home Loan July2017 - March2018 (8 Months) Home Loan Cross Sells,Lead Generation,Customer Cordination For Sanction & Disbursement.

4.RUDRAKSHA PVT. LTD.LUCKNOW

Team Leader - Tiles & Ceramics
Sales April2016 - June2017
(1Years 2Months)
Tiles and Sainatary Ware Sales, Team Handling, Project
Sales, Institutional Sales, Pay Collection, Proper Execution Of Order
And Dispatch It On Time. Followup For Payment. Develop New
Sample for Client . Maintain Good Relation With Client.

5. AMJ SALES PVT LTD. LUCKNOW

Sales Officer - Tiles And Ceramics Sales Feb2013 -March2016(3Years 1Month)

Tiles and Sainatary Ware Sales, Team Handling, Project Sales, Institutional Sales, Pay Collection, Proper Execution Of Order And Dispatch It On Time. Followup For Payment. Develop New Sample for Client . Maintain Good Relation With Client.

TECHNICAL QUALIFICATION

- Basic Fundamental Of Computer.
- MS Office & Internet Computer Course.
- Gold Auditor Certification.
- IRDA Certification.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

- Graduate (B.A.) with Second Division from Dr. Ram Manohar Loahia Awadh University Faizabad.
- Intermediate from UP Board(Science) with Second Division.
- High School from UP Board with Second Division.

STRENGTH

Positive
Thinking Hard
Working Result
Oriented

HOBBIES

Interaction with people Listening Music Traveling

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name : Mr. Krishna Bahadur Singh

Mother's Name : Mrs. Maya Singh

Date Of Birth : 01.01.1982

Gender : Male

Home Town : Lucknow Marital Status : Married

Category/Religion : General/Hindu

Languages known : Hindi -

Read, Write, Speak English - Read, Write

Permanent Address : Hno:166, Vahisthpuram, 60 Feet

Road, Behind Brahma

Kumari

Ashram, Jankipuram Lucknow-226021

Current Address : Vill- Imiriti Vishen, Bahraich

Road Post:- Bargaon, Gonda,

U.P 271002

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that all the above information is true to the best of my knowledge.

Date: VIJAY SINGH

Lucknow